Picture Collection LSC.0099.a
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Riley, Bennet, 1787-1853, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Rimpau Family -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Rinehart, Mary (Roberts), 1876-1958., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Rio Vista, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 4)
- Rivera Family -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 5)
- Rivers., 6 items (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Riverside -- Views., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Riverside, Calif. -- Views (Agriculture)., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Riverside, Calif. -- Views (Buildings)., 17 items (Folder 9)
- Riverside, Calif. -- Views (Churches)., 3 items (Folder 10)
- Riverside, Calif. -- Views (Mission Inn)., 133 items (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Riverside, Calif. -- Views (Mount Rubidoux)., 10 items (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Riverside, Calif. -- Views (Parks)., 2 items (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Riverside, Calif. -- Views (Residences)., 6 items (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Riverside, Calif. -- Views (Schools)., 4 items (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Riverside, Calif. -- Views (Streets)., 12 items (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Riverside, Calif. -- Views (Transportation)., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Roads -- Calif. (see also: Express Highways -- Los Angeles)., 17 items (Folder 18)
- Roberson, Hammond., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Roberts, Elizabeth Madox, 1886-1941, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Roberts, Frederick Sleigh Roberts, 1st earl, 1832-1914., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Roberts, Morley, 1857-1942, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Robertson, Federick William., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Robinson, Alfred., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Robinson, Ellen Lawless (Ternan) "Mrs. George Wharton Robinson" 1839-1914, -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Robinson, James W., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Robinson, Joseph Taylor, 1872-1937., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Robinson, Sir William [fl. 1690]., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 28)
- Robinson, William Wilcox, 1891-, 3 items (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Roche, Eng., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 30)
- Rockefeller, John Davison, 1839-1937., 1 item (Box 64, Folder 31)
- Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich, 1908-1979, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 32)
- Rocky Ford, Colo. -- Views., 15 items (Folder 33)
- Rocky Mountain National Park -- Views., 90 items (Folder 34)
- Rocky Mountains., 35 items (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Rodgers, Calbraith Perry, 1879-1912, -- Portrait., 7 items (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Roditi, Edouard, 1910-1992, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 5)
- Rogerio., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Rogers, Robert., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Rogers, Will, 1879-1935., 3 items (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Rolph, James., 2 items (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Romania -- Views., 99 items (Folder 7)
- Rome., 28 items (Folder 8)
- Romo, Ricardo -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Romulo, Carlos Pena, 1899-1985., 1 item (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Roosevelt, Dam Arizona -- Views., 1 item (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962, -- Portriat., 4 items (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, pres. U.S., 1882-1945., 4 items (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919, -- Portrait. (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Roosevelt, Theodore, pres. U.S., 1858-1919., 44 items (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Roper, Daniel Calhoun, 1867-1943., 1 item (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Rosa, Jose de la., 3 items (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Rosas Family., 1 item (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Rosecrans, William Starke, 1819-1898., 9 items (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Ross, E.M., 1 item (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Rossetti, Christina Georgina, 1830-1894., 8 items (Folder 20)
- Rossetti, Dante Gabriel, 1828-1882., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Roswell, N.M. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Rothstein, Arthur, 1915-1985, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 65, Folder 23)
- Rotor Ships -- Views., 1 item (Box 65, Folder 24)
- Rowland, John, Family -- Portrait., 9 items (Folder 25)
- Royal Gorge, Colo. -- Views., 34 items (Folder 26)
- Roybal, Edward Ross, 1916-2005., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Rubio (Jose) Adobe, Los Angeles -- Views., 1 item (Box 65, Folder 28)
- Rudhyar, Dane, 1895-1985., 1 item (Box 65, Folder 29)
- Ruef, Abraham, 1865?-1936, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 30)
- Ruetter, Andrew., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Ruggles, Charles -1892., 2 items (Folder 32)
- Ruiz Family -- Portrait., 8 items (Box 65, Folder 33)
- Rumcker Family., 17 items (Box 65, Folder 34)
- Ruse, E.L., 1 item (Folder 35)
- Ruskin, John., 2 items (Folder 36)
- Russell, William Clark, 1844-1911., 1 item (Folder 37)
- Russia -- Views., 13 items (Box 65, Folder 38)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 1 of 6) (Folder 6)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 2 of 6) (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 3 of 6) (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 4 of 6) (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 4 of 6) (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 4 of 6) (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 4 of 6) (Folder 8)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 4 of 6) (Folder 5)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 4 of 6) (Folder 6)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 5 of 6) (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Russia -- Views. (folder 6 of 6) (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Russian River -- Views., 1 item (Folder 1)
- Ruth, Nev. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 2)
- Rutledge, Wiley, 1894-1949., 2 items (Folder 3)
- Sabatini, Rafael, 1875-1950, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Sacramento River -- Views., 2 items (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Sacramento Valley Railroad., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Sacramento., 27 items (Folder 5)
- Sadleir, Michael, 1888-1957., 3 items (Folder 8)
- Sadler, Sir Michael Ernest, 1861-1943., 1 item (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Saguache, Colo. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Sailboats -- Views., 4 items (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Sailing Ships -- Views., 10 items (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Sainsevain, Jean L., 1 item (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Saint George, Utah -- Views., 9 items (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Saint Helena, Mount, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Saint Helena., 16 items (Folder 15)
- Saint Mary's College, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 17)
- Sainz, Amanda Garcia de, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Salem, Ore. -- Views., 1 item (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Salgado, Adelaida, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Salida, Colo. -- Views., 13 items (Folder 21)
- Salinas, Calif. -- Views., 28 items (Folder 22)
- Salt Lake City -- Views., 39 items (Folder 23)
- Salt River Valley, Arizona., 1 item (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Salton Sea., 4 items (Box 66, Folder 25)
- Salvini, Tommaso, 1829-1916, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Samoa -- Views., 12 items (Folder 27)
- Samuel Springs, Napa County, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 28)
- San Antonio, Mt., 4 items (Box 66, Folder 29)
- San Antonio, Texas., 4 items (Box 66, Folder 30)
- San Bernardino Mountains., 5 items (Folder 32)
- San Bernardino., 23 items (Folder 31)
- San Bernardino, Calif. -- Views. (Box 98, Folder 9)
- San Carlos Church, Monterey, Calif., 19 items (Box 66, Folder 33)
- San Clemente Island, Calif., 8 items (Box 67, Folder 2)
- San Clemente, Calif., 42 items (Folder 1)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Beaches)., 3 items (Folder 4)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Buildings)., 29 items (Folder 5)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Cabrillo National Monument)., 1 item (Box 67, Folder 6)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Churches)., 1 item (Box 67, Folder 7)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Flume)., 7 items (Box 67, Folder 8)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Harbor)., 10 items (Box 67, Folder 9)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Hotels)., 26 items (Box 67, Folder 10)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Mission Valley)., 1 item (Box 67, Folder 11)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Old Town)., 93 items (Box 67, Folder 12)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Panama-California Exposition, 1915-1916). Folder 1 of 3., 119 items (Folder 1)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Panama-California Exposition, 1915-1916). Folder 2 of 3., 103 items (Box 68, Folder 2)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Panama-California Exposition, 1915-1916). Folder 3 of 3. (Box 68, Folder 3)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Parks)., 18 items (Box 68, Folder 4)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Residences)., 3 items (Box 68, Folder 5)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Schools)., 9 items (Box 68, Folder 6)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Skyline)., 7 items (Box 68, Folder 7)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Streets)., 16 items (Box 68, Folder 8)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Torrey Pines)., 2 items (Box 68, Folder 9)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views (Transportation)., 5 items (Folder 10)
- San Diego, Calif. -- Views., 15 items (Folder 3)
- San Fernando Valley., 114 items (Box 69, Folder 1)
- San Fernando, Calif. -- Views., 18 items (Box 68, Folder 11)
- San Francisco -- Views (Beaches)., 3 items (Box 69, Folder 4)
- San Francisco -- Views (Buildings)., 9 items (Folder 5)
- San Francisco -- Views (California Midwinter International Exposition, 1894)., 2 items (Folder 6)
- San Francisco -- Views (China Town)., 18 items (Box 69, Folder 7)
- San Francisco -- Views (Churches)., 5 items (Box 69, Folder 8)
- San Francisco -- Views (Civic Center)., 12 items (Box 69, Folder 9)
- San Francisco -- Views (Cliff House)., 15 items (Folder 10)
- San Francisco -- Views (Earthquake and fire, 1906)., 67 items (Folder 11)
- San Francisco -- Views (Fort Winfield Scott)., 3 items (Box 69, Folder 12)
- San Francisco -- Views (Golden Gate International Exposition, 1939-1940)., 20 items (Box 69, Folder 14)
- San Francisco -- Views (Golden Gate Park)., 23 items (Box 70, Folder 1)
- San Francisco -- Views (Golden Gate)., 2 items (Box 69, Folder 13)
- San Francisco -- Views (Hotels)., 9 items (Box 70, Folder 2)
- San Francisco -- Views (Panama-Pacific International Exposition, 1915)., 139 items (Box 70, Folder 3)
- San Francisco -- Views (Parks)., 3 items (Box 70, Folder 4)
- San Francisco -- Views (Schools)., 5 items (Folder 5)
- San Francisco -- Views (Skylines)., 17 items (Folder 6)
- San Francisco -- Views (Streets)., 25 items (Box 70, Folder 9)
- San Francisco -- Views (Sutro Baths)., 3 items (Box 70, Folder 7)
- San Francisco -- Views (Sutro Heights)., 1 item (Folder 8)
- San Francisco -- Views., 17 items (Folder 3)
- San Francisco Bay -- Views., 13 items (Folder 10)
- San Francisco Peaks, Arizona., 2 items (Box 69, Folder 2)
- San Francisquito Canyon, Calif., 73 items (Box 70, Folder 11)
- San Gabriel Mountains., 8 items (Box 71, Folder 2)
- San Gabriel., 92 items (Box 71, Folder 1)
- San Jacinto Mountains -- Views., 1 item (Box 71, Folder 4)
- San Jacinto Valley, Calif., 1 item (Box 71, Folder 5)
- San Jacinto, Calif., 8 items (Box 71, Folder 3)
- San Jose, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 6)
- San Juan Bautista., 3 items (Folder 7)
- San Juan Capistrano., 12 items (Folder 8)
- San Luis Obispo., 21 items (Box 71, Folder 9)
- San Mateo, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Box 71, Folder 10)
- San Pasqual Valley, Calif., 2 items (Folder 12)
- San Pasqual, San Diego Co., Calif., 2 items (Folder 11)
- San Pedro, Calif., 48 items (Folder 13)
- San Rafael, Calif. -- Views., 11 items (Box 71, Folder 14)
- San Remo -- Views., 1 item (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Sanchez Family -- Portrait., 4 items (Folder 16)
- Sand, George, 1804-1876, -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 17)
- Sandburg, Carl., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Santa Ana., 2 items (Box 71, Folder 19)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views (Beach)., 7 items (Box 71, Folder 21)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views (Buildings)., 84 items (Folder 1)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views (Churches)., 4 items (Folder 2)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views (Earthquake, 1925)., 36 items (Folder 3)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views (Festivals)., 1 item (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views (Harbor)., 5 items (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views (Hospitals)., 6 items (Folder 6)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views (Hotels)., 70 items (Folder 7)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views (Residences)., 34 items (Folder 8)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views (Streets)., 3 items (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Santa Barbara, Calif. -- Views., 70 items (Box 71, Folder 20)
- Santa Catalina Island -- Views. Folder 1 of 3., 85 items (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Santa Catalina Island -- Views. Folder 2 of 3., 52 items (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Santa Catalina Island -- Views. Folder 3 of 3., 38 items (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Santa Catalina Island, Calif. -- Views. (Folder 6)
- Santa Clara University., 1 item (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Santa Clara Valley, Calif., 3 items (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Santa Clara, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Santa Cruz Island -- Views., 1 item (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Santa Cruz., 16 items (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Santa Fe, New Mexico., 167 items (Folder 7)
- Santa Maria, Calif., 7 items (Folder 8)
- Santa Monica -- Views (Ostrich Farms)., 1 item (Folder 2)
- Santa Monica -- Views. Folder 1 of 3., 35 items (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Santa Monica -- Views. Folder 2 of 3., 37 items (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Santa Monica -- Views. Folder 3 of 3., 41 items (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Santa Monica Canyon, Calif. -- Views., 35 items (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Santa Monica, California. (Box 96, Folder 11)
- Santa Paula, Calif. -- Views., 17 items (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Santa Rita, N.M. -- Views., 37 items (Folder 4)
- Santa Rosa Valley, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 7)
- Santa Rosa, Calif. -- Views. (Folder 5)
- Santa Rosa, Calif. -- Views., 7 items (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Santa Rosa, N.M. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 6)
- Santa Ynez Valley, Calif., 3 items (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Santayana, George, 1863-1952, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Santiago Canyon, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Sapinero, Colo. -- Views., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Saraste, Pablo Martin Meliton de, 1844-1910, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Sardou, Victorien., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Saroyan, William, 1908-1981., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Sarton George, 1884-1956, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Sausalito, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Scattergood, Ezra F., 1871-1947., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 17)
- Scheidemantel -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Schiller, Johann Christoph Friedrich von, 1759-1805., 2 items (Folder 19)
- Schipa, Tito, 1889-1965, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 20)
- Schneider, Walter Oto, 1895-1962, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 21)
- Schumacher, John -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 22)
- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 23)
- Schwab, Charles M., 1862-1939, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Schweitzer, Albert, 1875-1965., 2 items (Folder 25)
- Scotland., 22 items (Box 74, Folder 26)
- Scott, Clement William, 1841-1904, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 27)
- Scott, Jonathan R., 1 item (Folder 28)
- Scott, Sir Walter, Bart., 1771-1832., 2 items (Folder 30)
- Scott, Walter, 1872-1954., 2 items (Folder 29)
- Scott, Winfield, Editor., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 31)
- Sculpture, Modern -- 20th Century -- Views., 14 items (Box 74, Folder 32)
- Seattle -- Views., 2 items (Folder 33)
- Seidl, Anton, 1850-1898, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 34)
- Seigler Hot Springs, Calif. -- Views., 38 items (Folder 35)
- Seminario del Patrocinio de San Jose, Natividad, Monterey County, Calif., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 36)
- Sepulveda Family., 29 items (Box 74, Folder 37)
- Sequia National Park., 4 items (Box 74, Folder 38)
- Sequoia National Park -- Views. (Folder 1)
- Sergeant, Adeline, 1851-1904, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 74, Folder 39)
- Serra, Junipero, Father, 1713-1784., 9 items (Box 74, Folder 40)
- Serrano, Jose., 1 item (Folder 41)
- Seton, Ernest Thompson, 1860-1946, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 42)
- Severance, Caroline Maria., 2 items (Folder 43)
- Shaliapin, Fedor Ivanovich, 1873-1938, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Shantz, Homer LeRoy, 1876-1958, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Shasta County, Calif., 2 items (Folder 4)
- Shasta Springs, Calif., 8 items (Folder 6)
- Shasta, Mount -- Views. (Folder 10)
- Shasta, Mount., 8 items (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Shasta., 26 items (Folder 3)
- Shaw, Anna Howard, 1847-1919, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Shaw, Bernard, 1856-1950, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Shaw, Frank L., 1877-1958, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Shelley, Mary Woolstonecraft (Godwin), 1797-1851, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Shepherd, Harold C., 1 item (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Sheridan, Philip Henry, 1831-1888., 2 items (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Ship Models -- Views., 9 items (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Ships -- Views (M.S. Queen Mary)., 12 items (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Ships -- Views (S.S. Santa Elena)., 11 items (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Ships -- Views (U.S.S. Constitution)., 6 items (Box 75, Folder 17)
- Ships -- Views., 53 items (Folder 14)
- Ships -- Views. (folder 1 of 2) (Box 96, Folder 12)
- Ships -- Views. (folder 2 of 2) (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Shortridge, Samuel Morgan, 1861-1952., 1 item (Box 75, Folder 18)
- Shoshone Canyon, Wyomning -- Views., 2 items (Box 75, Folder 19)
- Shuler, Robert Pierce, 1880-1965, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 20)
- Siddons, Mrs. Sarah (Kemble)., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Sierra Madre., 7 items (Folder 22)
- Sierra Nevada Mountains., 14 items (Box 75, Folder 23)
- Sierra Valley, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 75, Folder 24)
- Silent, Charles. 1842-1918., 1 item (Folder 25)
- Silliphant, Stirling, 1918-1996, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Silver City, N.M. -- Views., 44 items (Folder 27)
- Sinclair, Mary Craig (Kimbrough), -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 75, Folder 28)
- Sinclair, Upton Beall, 1878-1968., 18 items (Box 75, Folder 29)
- Sinclair, Upton Bealle, 1878-1968, -- Portrait. (Folder 6)
- Sir Michael Ernst, 1861-1943, -- Portrait. (Folder 10)
- Siskiyou Mountains, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 30)
- Sittel Family -- Portrait., 15 items (Box 75, Folder 31)
- Sitwell, Dame Edith, 1887-1964, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Slaughter, Fenton M., 1826-1897, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 2)
- Slave Trade -- Views., 2 items (Folder 4)
- Slavery - United States - Children., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Sloan, Helen Mary, 13 items (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Slotterbeck, H., 1 item (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Smedley, Francis Edward, 1818-1864., 2 items (Folder 7)
- Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1873-1944., 9 items (Folder 8)
- Smith, Chard Powers, 1894- -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Smith, Gypsy -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Smith, Jack Clifford, 1916-1996, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Smith, Paul Jordan, 1885-1971., 7 items (Folder 11)
- Smith, Wilbur Jordan, 1906- -- Portrait., 4 items (Folder 12)
- Smitter, Wessel, 1894- -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Smyth, Albert Henry, 1863-1907., 2 items (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Snake River., 2 items (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Snyder, Meredith Pinxton, 1859-1937., 2 items (Folder 17)
- Soboba Hot Springs, Calif. -- Views., 20 items (Folder 18)
- Socorro, N.M. -- Views., 32 items (Folder 19)
- Somervell, Brehon Burke, 1892-1955., 1 item (Box 76, Folder 20)
- Sonoma, Calif., 11 items (Box 76, Folder 21)
- Sonora, Calif., 8 items (Folder 22)
- Sousa, John Philip, 1854-1932, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 23)
- South Africa -- Views., 9 items (Folder 24)
- South Dakota -- Views., 15 items (Box 76, Folder 25)
- South Dakota -- Views. (folder 1 of 3) (Folder 13)
- South Dakota -- Views. (folder 2 of 3) (Box 96, Folder 14)
- South Dakota -- Views. (folder 3 of 3) (Box 100, Folder 7)
- South Pasadena, Calif., 3 items (Box 76, Folder 26)
- South Pasadena, Calif. -- Bilicke Mansion -- Views., 74 items (Box 76, Folder 27)
- South Pasadena, Calif. -- Ostrich Farm -- Views., 6 items (Box 76, Folder 28)
- Southwest, New., 29 items (Folder 29)
- Souvenir Photographs -- Views., 12 items (Folder 30)
- Spadra., 2 items (Folder 1)
- Spain -- Views., 10 items (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Sparks, Isaac J., 1 item (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Sparks, Nev. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Spence, E.F., 2 items (Folder 5)
- Spencer, Herbert, 1820-1903, -- Portrait., 26 items (Folder 6)
- Spinoza, Benedictus de, 1632-1677, -- Portrait. (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Spinoza, Benedictus de, 1632-1677, -- Portrait., 5 items (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Sports -- Views., 7 items (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Springer, N.M. -- Views., 3 items (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Sri Lanka -- Views., 1 item (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Stanford University., 163 items (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Stanford, Leland, 1824-1893., 2 items (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Stanley, Timothy Robbins, 1810-1874., 1 item (Folder 13)
- Stannard, Mrs. Henrietta Eliza Vaughan (Palmer), 1856-1911., 2 items (Folder 14)
- Stark, James Douglas -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Starrett, Vincent, 1886-1974, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Stead, William thomas, 1849-1912, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 77, Folder 17)
- Steamboat Springs, Colo. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 18)
- Stearns, Abel, 1799-1871., 2 items (Folder 19)
- Steel Industry and Trade -- Views., 11 items (Folder 20)
- Stein, Gertrude, 1874-1946., 23 items (Box 77, Folder 21)
- Steinbeck, John, 1902-1968., 2 items (Box 77, Folder 22)
- Stephens, William Dennison, 1859-1944., 1 item (Folder 23)
- Steptoe, Nev. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Sterling, George, 1869-1926., 2 items (Folder 25)
- Stevenson, Adlai, Ewing, 1900-1965, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 77, Folder 26)
- Stevenson, Robert Louis, 1850-1894., 2 items (Box 77, Folder 27)
- Stillman, Jacob Davis Babock, 1819-1888., 1 item (Folder 28)
- Stimpson, Henry Lewis, 1867-1960., 2 items (Folder 30)
- Stimson, Marshall, Family -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 29)
- Stock, Robert., 1 item (Box 77, Folder 31)
- Stockton, Calif. -- Views., 37 items (Box 77, Folder 33)
- Stockton, Robert Field., 4 items (Folder 32)
- Stone, Harlan Fiske, 1872-1946, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 34)
- Stone, Marcus., 1 item (Folder 35)
- Stonewall Mine, San Diego Co., Calif., 2 items (Box 77, Folder 36)
- Story, F.Q., 1 item (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Stowe, Harriet Elizabeth (Beecher), 1811-1896, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 2)
- Stratton, Dorothy Constance, 1899-2006., 1 item (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Stratton, Lavinia (Warren)., 1 item (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Strauss Johann, 1825-1899., 2 items (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Strawberry Lake, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Street -- Railroads -- Views., 8 items (Folder 8)
- Street, Julian Leonard, 18789-1947., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Streeter, Ruth Cheney, 1895-1990, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Stretton, Hesba, 1832-1911., 1 item (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Strobridge, Ida Meacham., 2 items (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Subiaco, Italy -- Views., 2 items (Folder 12)
- Summerall, Charles Pelot, 1867-1955., 1 item (Folder 13)
- Summerland, Calif., 2 items (Folder 14)
- Sumner Family., 5 items (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Surveying -- Instruments -- Views., 3 items (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Susanville., 1 item (Folder 17)
- Sutro Alfred., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Sutter Creek, Calif., 1 item (Folder 20)
- Sutter, John A., 2 items (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Sutter, John Augustus, 1803-1880, -- Portrait. (Folder 1)
- Sutter's Fort State Historical Monument, Sacramento, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Swallow, George Clinton, 1817-1899., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Swanick, Anna, 1813-1899., 1 item (Box 78, Folder 23)
- Sweden -- Views., 69 items (Box 78, Folder 24)
- Swerling, Jo, 1897-1964., 3 items (Folder 25)
- Swett, John., 2 items (Folder 26)
- Swinburne, Algernon., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Switzerland -- Views., 8 items (Box 78, Folder 28)
- Sylmar, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Box 78, Folder 29)
- Taft, Calif. -- Views., 25 items (Folder 30)
- Taft, William Howard, 1857-1930., 25 items (Folder 31)
- Taggard, Genevieve, 1894-1948, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 32)
- Tahoe, Lake -- Views (Camp Agassiz)., 3 items (Box 78, Folder 34)
- Tahoe, Lake -- Views (Emeraldn Bay)., 6 items (Box 78, Folder 35)
- Tahoe, Lake -- Views (Fallen Leaf Lake)., 15 items (Folder 36)
- Tahoe, Lake -- Views (Falls)., 11 items (Folder 37)
- Tahoe, Lake -- Views (Glen Alpine Springs)., 7 items (Folder 38)
- Tahoe, Lake -- Views (Grass Lake)., 4 items (Box 78, Folder 39)
- Tahoe, Lake -- Views (Hotels)., 31 items (Box 78, Folder 40)